■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录www.Deefun.com
■
翻译： zxm.  Sue_suki
校订： Enpistu
■
后期： Enpistu  liloelva
好啊  大家
Howdy, Duncans.
-嗨  -嗨  博
- Hey. - Hey, Beau.
-早上好啊  甜心  -早上好
- Morning, Sweetie. - Hi.
今天会是很棒的一天  小博
We got a big day ahead of us, little B.
我很期待  老鲍
I'm looking forward to it, big B.
很好  他们都有爱称了
Oh. Good. They have nicknames.
好了  该出门了
Yeah, I guess we should get going.
今天我们要去捅一个蜂窝
Taking down a hornet's nest today.
怪不得我都感受到空气中的兴奋了
So that's the excitement I feel in the air.
听着  有个惊喜给你
Oh, hey. Got a surprise for you.
我准备让你拿着喷雾器
I am gonna let you hold the fogger.
请允许我拥抱你吧  先生
Permission to hug you, Sir.
哦  来吧  小博
Oh, bring it in, little B.
-好了  再见  各位  -回见  女孩们
- All right. We'll see you guys. - See you girls.
再见
See ya.
我觉得你爸爸真的很喜欢这小子
I think your father really likes this one.
我知道
I know.
这真让我烦恼
It concerns me.
哦  我得去学校了
Well, I should probably get to school.
好的  过的愉快  小泰
All right. Have a good day, little T.
你也一样  老艾
You too, big A.
生活搞得一团糟
Today's all burnt toast
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
Running late, and dad jokes
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
Has anybody seen my left shoe
我闭上眼  咬口早餐
I close my eyes, take a bite
跳上车子  放声大笑
Grab a ride, laugh out loud
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
There it is up on the roof
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
I've been there, I've survived
所以听取我的建议
So just take my advice
宝贝  不要放弃
Hang in there, baby
世界有很多疯狂无奈
Things are crazy
可是我知道你会有美好将来
But I know your future's bright
宝贝  不要放弃
Hang in there, baby
不要怀疑
There's no maybe
一切终会如你所愿
Everything turns out all right
生活有悲有喜
Sure life is up and down
但是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
But trust me it comes back around
你会喜欢将来的你
You're gonna love who you turn out to be
宝贝  不要放弃
Hang in there, baby.
查莉成长日记  第四季第十六集
Good Luck Charlie  S04E16  Bob's Beau-Be-Gone
埃米特  我们要付房租了
Emmett, we gotta pay our rent.
又要付
Again?
这算啥  现在每个月都得交了
What is that, like every month now?
-是的  -但我现在没钱
- Yeah. - But I don't have the money right now.
哦  你真是太不可靠了
Well, that is very irresponsible.
特别是  我也没有钱
Especially since I don't either.
-好吧  那我们该咋办  -不知道
- Well, what are we gonna do? - I don't know.
但是如果我们付不了房租
But if we can't pay the rent on this place we're
我们就得搬回去和爸妈住
gonna have to move back home with our parents.
你还可以搬回去  我就没地儿待了
Well maybe you can, but that's not an option for me.
为什么
Why not?
我爸妈搬家了  还不肯告诉我搬哪儿去了
My parents moved and they won't tell me where.
那  如果你想看他们怎么办
Well, what if you want to see them?
另找一个中立的地方见喽
Oh, we meet at a neutral location.
但是我得先走  这样确保我不能跟踪他们
But I have to leave first so that way I can't follow them.
好吧  如果我们付不了房租
Well, if we're having trouble paying the rent,
或许可以考虑找一个室友
maybe we could get a roommate.
你是说  找个其他人住这儿
You mean like somebody else that would live here?
那就是室友  是的
That's what a roommate is, yes.
赞啊  好主意
Well, that's a great idea.
这样我们就可以每人支付三分之一的房租了
That way we'd each only have to pay one third of the rent.
等会儿  我算的对么
Wait, did I do that math right?
就好像我知道似的
Like I'd know.
-小心那个机械人  -我看见了
- Oh, watch out for that cyborg. - I see him.
灭了他
Got him.
你真冷酷  我就喜欢这点
You are ruthless. I love it.
-从我外婆那继承来的  -还是很喜欢
- I get it from my Grandma. - I still love it.
喂  孩子们
Hey, kids.
有什么事吗  邓肯阿姨
Something wrong, Mrs. Duncan?
噢  又来了
Oh, here we go.
既然你问了
Well... since you asked.
看  我是个地方电视名人
See, I'm a local television personality.
我在"早安丹佛"中出场过
I appear on "Good Morning Denver".
然后话匣子就打开了
And the flood gates are open.
但是他们最近都没让我上场过
But they haven't had me on lately,
这真让我失望
and it is really getting me down.
难道我的名人生涯就这么结束了吗
Is it over for me?
但我还有好多才艺没有带给观众们啊
While I still have so much left to give?
你知道  这真是一个好问题
You know, that's a really good question.
也许爸爸知道答案
Maybe Dad knows the answer to that.
爸  妈妈要过去了
Dad! Here comes Mom.
好吧好吧  现在全是在说绿色杂货店了
Yeah yeah yeah. It's all about the Green Grocer.
他是这个月的新星
He's the flavor of the month.
我觉得他仅仅是靠运气
I think he just got lucky
就因"吃着西葫芦  穿着比基尼"这一句话
with that "Eat a zucchini, wear a bikini" Line.
噢  我外婆也看了那个部分
Oh, my Grandma saw that segment.
她还专门为此去买了西葫芦呢
And then she bought some zucchini.
她该不会还想
She's not thinking of...
比基尼  噢  千万不要
A bikini? Oh, I don't think so.
坚持住
Stay on top of that.
我明天也会有一段出场
I actually have a segment coming on tomorrow.
这是我这几个星期的第一次出场
It's my first one in weeks.
可是会不会成为最后一次啊
But will it be my last?
爸  妈妈的问题都成堆了
Dad, these questions from Mom are piling up!
好吧
Oh well.
如果这真是我的最后一次  我想
If it is my last, I guess the
好消息就是我有更多的时间陪孩子们了
good news is I get to spend more time with my kids.
你的那一场是表演什么
What's your segment about?
嗯
Okay.
是一个能哄小孩子开心
It's about entertaining the
又能完成家务的妙招
little ones and also getting your housework done.
我所做的就是把毛巾折成了有趣的动物形状
What I do is I fold towels into whimsical animal shapes.
有很强的视觉效果
A lot of it is visual.
-这样  想我给你看看么  -好啊
- Here, want me to show you? - Sure.
好的  太棒了  我刚做了一个  你会喜欢它的
Okay, great. I just made one. You'll love it.
你出啥毛病了  我本以为你很冷酷的
What is wrong with you? I thought you said you were ruthless.
那是对机械人
With cyborgs.
-可是那是你妈  -有什么区别
- This is your Mom. - What's the difference?
看招
Ba-bam!
这是一只天鹅
It's a swan!
想要看看我是怎么做的吗
Do you want me to show you how?
来吧  小鬼们  我有一篮子的
Come on, guys. I've got a
毛巾和大把的时间
basket full of towels and nothing but time.
-嗨  -嗨  伙计们
- Hey. - Hey, guys.
泰迪  今天发生了一件特别神奇的事情
Teddy, the most amazing thing happened today.
我第一次看见了骆驼蟋蟀
I saw my first camel cricket.
你得知道  这孩子是一个天才
You know, this kid is a natural.
我本以为那是洞穴蟋蟀
I thought it was a cave cricket.
哇  你当时肯定回头
Wow. Well, I hope you turned
给我爸一个轻蔑的"你错了"
to my Dad and gave him a big old "In your face!"
呃  不会啊  我们可是一队的
Yeah, we don't do that. We're a team.
对  除非我们被臭鼬攻击了
Well, unless we're getting attacked by a skunk.
那还是大难临头各自飞吧
Then you're on your own.
不仅是出色的灭虫专家  还有很棒的幽默感
A great exterminator and a great sense of humor.
噢  别说啦
Oh, stop.
博  甜心  你已经得到工作了
Beau, honey, you got the job.
你不用再迎合他了
You can stop kissing up and
你可以像我们一样寻他开心了
start making fun of him like the rest of us.
你什么意思
What do you mean?
就是说  你不用再假装
It's just, you don't have to pretend to be
喜爱那些灭虫什么的东西了
fascinated with all of this exterminator stuff.
但是  我是真的喜欢啊
But I really am fascinated.
我都能想象这是在做我毕生的事业
I could see myself doing this as a career.
你认真的吗
Seriously?
是啊  对  今天我不是去地下室了吗
Yeah. Um... today I was in the crawlspace, right?
-然后我发现了一只很大的老蜘蛛  -博  博
- And I found this big old spider... - Beau Beau...
就像我妈经常说的那样
As my Mom always says,
不管房子下面发生什么  就让它深埋在地下吧
what happens under the house stays under the house.
-好吧  我想我该走了  -好的
- All right. Well, I'd better go. - Okay.
我得回家洗个澡
I need to get home and get showered.
我们今天用来杀虫的东西可是有剧毒的
That stuff we were using today is highly toxic.
你就不能在抱我之前就说吗
Could you have maybe told me that before the hug?
嗯  你大概也得去洗个澡了
Yeah, you're probably gonna have to shower too.
抱歉  甜心
Sorry, Sweetie.
-嘿  博去哪儿啦  -他刚走
- Hey. Where's Beau? - Oh, he just left.
都没和我说再见就走了吗
Without saying good-bye?
爸  你明天就能见到他了
Dad, you'll see him again tomorrow...
在那些讨厌的狭小的封闭空间
In some disgusting little enclosure.
我告诉你  博真的是一个很好的孩子
I'm telling you. That Beau is a great kid.
而且大家都知道
And who knows.
你们俩在一起了  我以后
You two stick together, I could
就可以把我的事业交给他了
see passing the business down to him some day.
爸  我们还没有交往多久呢
Dad, we haven't been dating for that long.
我知道  只是
I know. It's just...
这一个感觉很特别
This one feels special.
我有一个工程学的学位
So I have an engineering degree.
现在我正在攻读天体物理的博士学位
Now I'm working on my masters in astrophysics.
嗯  这都很好  布莱恩
Well, that's all well and good, Brian,
但是我们有个很严格的筛选程序
but we have a pretty strict screening process here.
所以我要问你一个很重要的问题
So let me ask you the big question.
你有
Do you have...
167美元吗
$167?
有啊
Yes.
好的  下一个问题
Okay. Follow-up question.
你下个月的这时候也有167美元吗
Will you have $167 this time next month?
-是的  -我们已经知道所有的信息了
- Yes. - I think we have all we need.
我很整洁  我很安静
I'm neat, I'm quiet.
那你对不整洁不安静的
And how do you feel about
室友怎么看
roommates who are neither neat nor quiet?
没关系  我只是需要一个住的地方
That's fine. I just need a place to live.
我们已经问过你关于167美元的问题了吗
And did we ask you about the $167 already?
刚刚问过了
A few times, yes.
好的  安迪  谢谢你过来
Okay, Andy. Thanks for coming over.
-我们会很快给你回复的  -好的
- We'll get back to you real soon. - Great.
嗯  看来选择已经很明显了
Well, seems to me the choice is obvious.
用脚想都知道
I'd say it's a no-brainer.
-同意  好样的  室友  -多谢
- I agree. Good job, roomie. - All right.
有一个新室友的生活一定很棒
It's gonna be nice having a new roommate.
多了一个帮我们做家务的家伙
One more guy to help with chores.
-多了一个帮我们购物的家伙  -还有最好的是
- One more guy to help with shopping. - And the best part is...
我们终于可以实现我们的梦想了
We can finally realize our dream.
叠罗汉
The human pyramid.
好了  这样听起来怎样
Okay, how does this sound?
"亲爱的台长 在最近的鸟妈妈节目中
"Dear station manager Mama Bird's
把毛巾做成动物的那一段真是太“巾采”了
recent segment on towel animals was towel-rific".
你在做什么
What are you doing?
我们在给"早安丹佛"写信
We're writing letters to "Good
这样他们就会把老妈留在台里
Morning Denver" So they'll keep mommy on TV,
重点是她就不会再来烦我们了
and most importantly away from us.
信是什么
What's a letter?
就是用一种又贵又慢的方式去寄电子邮件
It's an expensive way to slowly send an e-mail.
好了  我们有十封信了
Okay. We have 10 letters.
好的  让我们把这些放到信里
Okay. Let's get these things in the mail
这样它们会在妈妈的节目播出第二天寄到台里
so they'll arrive the day after Mom's story airs.
查莉  我想玩换装游戏了
Charlie, I'm ready to play dress-up.
来了
Coming.
希望你的信有效果
This better work.
小博
Beau Jr.
你吃得像你鲍伯爷爷一样
You eat just like grandpa Bob.
你有这么多牙齿了
And you have just as many teeth.
好啦
Yeah.
-嗨  亲爱的  -嗨  甜心
- Hey, darling. - Hi, honey.
还有你  小宝贝
And baby boy.
你知道  在漫长一天的杀虫工作后
You know, there's nothing I'd rather see after a
除了你这美丽的新娘  我什么都不想看了
long day of killing bugs than my beautiful bride.
噢  你在做饭
Oh, you're cooking.
是啊  生活难道不是很有意思吗
Yeah. Isn't it funny how life turned out?
我像我妈一样做饭  你像我爸一样工作
I cook like my Mom, and you work like my Dad.
但是除了这点  我和他完全不同
But other than that, me and him are pretty different.
你今天掉了更多的头发
You lose more hair today?
是啊
Yeah.
但我背后会长回来更多的
But more came in on my back.
哦  这真好
Oh. That's nice.
你不会相信今天我工作时发生了什么
You won't believe what happened at work today.
又是一个除虫故事吗
Is this gonna be a bug story?
是啊  本来是讲除虫的  但是后面有一只野猫的戏份
Yeah, it starts out as one, but then a feral cat comes into it.
我好像剧透太早了
I'm getting ahead of myself.
哦  甜心  慢慢讲
Oh, honey, take your time.
我哪儿也不会去
I'm not going anywhere.
永远
Ever.
那是在约翰逊家的地下室
There I was in the Johnson's crawlspace.
很平常的一个星期二
Ordinary Tuesday...
或者说  我以为很平常
Or so I thought.
直到我看见了木屑
Yeah. Until I saw the sawdust.
这意味着有白蚁
That always means termites.
是啊  通常是这样
Well, almost always.
天呐  我敢说这地方从未这么干净过
Man, I don't think the place has ever been this clean before.
是啊  真是高效的十五分钟
Yeah, that was a rough 15 minutes.
肯定是咱们的新室友来了
Ah. That must be our new roommate.
-嗨伙计们  -嗨
- Hi, guys. - Hi.
呃  安迪怎么来了
Uh, what's Andy doing here?
他是咱们的新室友啊
He's our new roommate.
他不是啊  布莱恩才是咱们的新室友
No, he's not. Brian's our new roommate.
-嘿  -我可不这么认为
- Hey. - I don't think so.
两位  进来吧
Guys, come on in.
我们要在走廊谈一小会儿
We're gonna have a quick discussion out in the hallway.
和你没关系的
Not about you.
和你有点儿关系
A little about you.
你不是说这事儿用脚想都行吗
I thought you said this was a no-brainer.
是啊  选那个矮个儿
Yeah, to pick the short guy.
他可是我们叠罗汉完美的顶端
He's the perfect top for the pyramid.
选那个高个儿咱们的叠罗汉会更高
The pyramid will be higher with the tall guy.
也许咱们不该任何事情都从叠罗汉的角度考虑
Maybe we shouldn't have based everything on the pyramid.
难以置信这几周我就上了这么一回电视
I can't believe this is the first time I've been on TV in weeks.
不对劲啊老妈  这事儿不科学
It's not right, Mom. It's just not right.
好  开始了
Okay. Here we go.
早安丹佛  早安菲尔
Good Morning, Denver. And good morning, Phil.
朗达  和你一起每早都安
It's always a good morning when I'm with you, Rhonda.
不得不说  我挺喜欢菲尔和朗达
I've got to say, I like Phil and Rhonda.
在幕后他们两个都受不了彼此
Behind the scenes, those two can't stand each other.
不是吧
No!
是的
Yes.
菲尔和朗达原来是一对情侣
Gabe, Phil and Rhonda used to be a couple.
直到朗达决定做绿色杂货店节目的情人
That is until Rhonda decided to give the Green Grocer a squeeze.
下面我们要报道几条重大新闻
We're getting word now of some breaking news.
请看I-70州际公路直播  在这里我们的直升机
Let's go live to I-70, where our news chopper
正在追踪拍摄一场高速的警方追捕
is following a high speed police pursuit.
什么  不要啊  人家要看妈咪
What? No, we want to see Mom!
盖比  亲爱的  别慌
Gabe. Honey, relax.
没关系的  我是压轴出场的
It's okay. I'm on towards the end.
只要这追捕不持续太久  就没问题
As long as this doesn't go on too long, we'll be fine.
这已经成为
This is now becoming one
丹佛史上历时最长的警方追捕
of the longest car chases in Denver history.
太糟糕了
Oh. This is bad.
这真是太糟糕了
This is really really bad.
怎么了
What's wrong?
是这样的  明天电视台会收到一沓儿信
Well, tomorrow the station's gonna get a bunch of letters
说他们如何喜欢老妈的故事  可是节目没有播出
saying how much they loved Mom's story which isn't on.
太糟糕了
This is bad.
这确实很糟糕
This is really bad.
这追捕还没结束吗
Is this chase still on?
是的  来人啊
Yes. Somebody!
让他靠边停车  爆他的轮胎
Pull him over, flatten his tires.
我们想看毛巾动物
We want to see towel animals!
盖比甜心  没事的
Gabe, honey, it's okay.
我们能挺过去的
We'll get through this.
如果他们今天不播我那段的话
If they don't put my segment on today,
总有一天会播的
they'll put it on another day.
不行  必须今天播
No, it has to be today.
看起来他靠边停车  举手投降了
Looks like he's pulling over, and he's putting his hands up.
看起来这场追逐已经和平结束了
Guess this chase has come to a peaceful ending.
好耶  终于结束了
Yes. Finally.
好了  我们还有段时间播另外一段
Well, we have time for one more segment.
我们把最好的留到了最后
And we saved the best for last.
所以接下来请收看大家的最爱  绿色杂货店
So let's hear from everybody's favorite, the Green Grocer.
你在逗我吗
Oh, come on!
-嘿亲爱的  -嘿
- Hey, darling. - Hey.
你怎么了
How are you?
我没事  就是做了个疯狂的梦
I'm okay, I guess. I had this crazy dream.
是关于未来  我们生活在了这里
It was the future, and we were living here.
你接管了我爸的事业
You inherited my Dad's business
还讲了些疯狂的除虫故事
and you were telling these crazy bug stories.
好有趣啊
That's funny.
而且你还秃顶
And you were bald.
这就不有趣了
That's not funny.
听着  我们坐下来好吗
Listen, can we sit?
有些事情我得跟你谈谈
I got something I need to talk to you about.
好吧
Yeah.
怎么了
What's going on?
拉尔夫・休斯死了
Ralph Hughes died.
噢不
Oh no.
谁是拉尔夫・休斯啊
Who's Ralph Hughes?
我不知道啊
I don't know.
好吧  很庆幸我们是为这事儿坐下来
Well, I'm really glad we sat down for this.
不  我只是没见过他而已
No, I mean I just never met him.
他本来是我家乡的除虫师
He was the exterminator back home in Hollow Rock.
也就是说这个职位有空档
Which means there's a job opening
而且如果我想要的话就是我的了
for an exterminator and it's mine if I want it.
我祖母打电话来
My Grandma called.
她说如果我接下这份工作回家去
She said if I take this job and come home,
她会支付我上夜校的费用
she'll pay for me to go to college at night.
那么你是在说  你要回田纳西去吗
So what are you saying? Are you going back to Tennessee?
我也不知道该如何回绝
I don't know how I can turn this down.
你看  我也不想说什么的
Look, I didn't want to say anything but...
可我真的有些想家了
I've been real homesick.
我喜欢给你爸爸工作可是
I like working for your Dad and all but...
泰迪
Teddy...
你是唯一能把我留在丹佛的人
The only thing that would keep me in Denver is you.
听着 博
Look, Beau...
我也不想让你走
I don't want you to go...
可我不愿成为你的阻碍
But I'm not gonna stand in your way.
那么
So...
是时候说再见了
This is good-bye?
我想是这样的
Yeah, I guess so.
你是个特别的女孩  泰迪
You're a special girl, Teddy.
我会一直想念你的
I'm gonna miss you a ton.
我也会想念你的
I'm gonna miss you too.
孩子们
Hey, guys.
怎么一脸悲伤的样子
Why the sad faces?
现在该是最艰难的时刻了
Now comes the hard part.
换人啦
Rotate.
布莱恩  你听见叮了没  叮一声我们就轮流换人啦
Brian, you heard the ding. After the ding, we rotate.
我还没吃完呢
I'm not done eating yet.
我不管 去厕所解决吧
I don't care. Take it to the bathroom.
这样多不卫生
That's not sanitary.
这样安排真不错
And the system works.
嘿PJ  你介不介意我
Hey PJ, you mind trading
用厕所时光换点儿你的座椅时光
me some bathroom time for some chair time?
规矩是这样的  叮 换 叮 换
The system is ding, move, ding, move.
除此之外没别的
There are no tack-ons.
-安迪  -别看我
- Andy? - Don't even look at me.
闪啦
Rotate.
埃米特  去厕所
Emmett, bathroom.
为啥  我很干净而且刷过牙  我根本不用去
Why? I'm clean, I'm brushed and I don't have to go.
不关我事  我们有规矩的
Not my problem. We have a system.
这规矩真愚蠢  我都看三个剧的开头了
The system's stupid. I've seen the beginnings of three shows.
却连一个剧的结局都不知道
I don't know how any of them end.
是谁从牙膏管的中间开始挤的
Who's squeezing the toothpaste tube from the middle?
我浪费了一半的厕所时光去弄好它
I wasted half my bathroom time trying to fix this.
PJ我能不能和你在走廊说句话
PJ, can I talk to you in the hallway please?
没问题
Sure.
你们俩继续听叮换人  我们去去就回
You guys keep moving on the dings, okay? We'll catch up.
换人啦
Rotate.
-这样下去不行  -是啊 你说的没错
- This isn't working. - Yeah, you're right.
咱们得弄走一个
We have to get rid of somebody.
-我选布莱恩  -我选安迪
- I pick Brian. - I pick Andy.
重新选
Re-vote.
-布莱恩  -安迪
- Brian. - Andy.
-重选  -不行啊伙计
- Re-vote. - No, man.
在我看来  只有一个方式解决这个问题了
As I see it, there's only one possible way to solve this.
我们离开这里
We're out of here.
没错  我们要找自己的地盘
Yeah. We're getting our own place.
好吧  两个方式
Well, two ways.
我知道现在你很难过
I know it's hard right now...
但是会有其他灭虫师的
But there will be other exterminators.
不
No.
都比不上博
Not like Beau.
他很特别的
He was special.
你会好起来的  我保证
You'll be okay, I promise.
你不明白啦
You don't understand.
没人会明白的
Nobody understands.
我以为他就是那个人呢
I thought he was the one.
可是  这不一定就是永别啊
Well, this doesn't have to be good-bye forever.
你可以视频聊天
You could video chat.
我不会视频聊天
I don't know how to do that.
我教你啊
I'll teach you.
真的吗
You will?
当然啦
Of course I will.
乖
Come here.
过来
为什么
Why?
我要给你一个拥抱
I want to give you a hug.
我需要更多信息量
I'm gonna need more information.
盖比  我刚刚和电视台经纪人通过电话
Gabe, I just got off the phone with the station manager.
他们收到了一大沓信
Yeah, they received a whole
关于我没播放的节目
bunch of letters about my segment that never aired.
我知道是你写的
And I know you wrote them.
-你知道  -是这两件事告诉我的
- You do? - Two things tipped me off.
第一  昨天看节目时
One, you were acting
你的表现非常奇怪
really weird when you were watching the show.
第二  你居然看节目了
And two, you were watching the show.
-你不生气吗  -不 亲爱的
- And you're not mad? - No, honey.
恰恰相反
Just the opposite.
我真不敢相信
I can't believe you would go to
为了帮妈咪延续电视生涯  你竟然揽下这么多麻烦
all that trouble to help your mommy's TV career.
这就是我所做的
That's exactly why I did it.
事实上  电视台经理非常受感动
In fact, the station manager was so impressed
他想要我做一期关于咱俩亲情的节目
he wants me to do a segment on our relationship.
他  他想干嘛
He... he wants what now?
讲述我们有多么的亲密
It'll be all about how close we are.
我要叫它  “我的宝贝盖比”
I'm gonna call it "My baby Gabey".
我们要穿配套的衣服
We're gonna wear matching outfits.
你是说真的吗  老妈
Are you for real, Mom?
还是在整我什么的
Or are you just messing with me or something?
我为啥要整我的宝贝盖比呢
Why would I mess with my baby Gabey?
因为你写那些信的真正目的
Because the real reason you wrote the letters
是把我赶出咱们家咩
was to get me out of the housey wousey?
-查莉告诉你的吧  -她像小鸟一样唱出来嘀
- Charlie told you? - She sang like a birdy wordy.
是这样的查莉  博搬回田纳西了
Well, Charlie, Beau moved back to Tennessee.
而且  尽管他
And even though he's only
才离开几天  我已经在想念他了
been gone a few days, I already miss him.
当然了  没有老爸那么想念
Of course, not as much as Dad does.
哇哦
Wow!
一个满是黄蜂的窝
A nest full of yellow jackets?!
喔噢
Whoa!
干的漂亮啊  小博
Good kill, little B.
是啊  名师出高徒嘛
Yeah, well, I learned from the best.
泰迪在吗
Is Teddy around?
呃  不在
Uh, nope.
还没回家呢  听着
No, not home yet. Um, hey, listen.
让我给你讲讲今天看见的黑寡妇蜘蛛
Let me tell you about this black widow spider I saw today.
她身上那个卵袋简直有垒球那么大
She had an egg sack on her the size of a softball.
我想这次给你的建议是
I guess my advice to you would be...
还是和一个怕虫子的男生约会吧  如果不是的话
Date a guy who's afraid of bugs because if not...
那么
Well...
祝你好运咯  小查莉
Good luck, Charlie.
你是个什么玩意
What are you supposed to be?
多明显啊  一只毛巾龙虾
A towel lobster, obviously.
呃  我没看出来
Huh! I'm not getting that.
也许更像螃蟹
Crab, maybe.
那么  你应该是什么
Well, what are you supposed to be?
我显然是只毛巾大象
I'm obviously a towel elephant.
叠得多像啊
And a pretty good one.
真的吗
Really?
我怎么看着像食蚁兽
I'm getting more anteater.
你们消停会儿行不行
Could you guys keep it down?
你是什么啊
Who are you supposed to be?
毛巾啊
A towel.
而且以此为荣  我才不需要那些装饰
And proud of it. I don't need all the bells and whistles.
听见了吗孩子  做自己才是最棒的
Hear that kids? It's okay to just be who you are.
你现在还喜欢做自己吗
How do you like who you are now?